howtodoinjava.com 2013-12-03

# Privacy policy | How to do in JAVA

## 

Select Page: 

Select Category: 

**What information do we collect?**

In this website, you are required to :  
1) enter your email address to get latest updates from this blog directly into your email box for free  
2) enter your name, email and website you own, when you put a comment on any post

Apart from this, you are not expected to put any personal information anywhere in this blog, including comments, which you may not want to make public.

**How do we use your information?**

This website will use your email addresses to send you notifications about new posts when they are published. You may also get weekly updates which will include all happenings in last week in form of a guide.

When you leave a comment of this website, you may get a notification regarding your comment approval/denial.

**Disclose of information**

I do not sell, trade, release, or otherwise transfer information partially or in its entirety to any third party unless pursuant of an investigation of suspected unlawful, harmful, or otherwise illegal activity (including enforcement of our site’s policies, protection to our rights, property, and/or safety or the rights, property, and/or safety of others), or strictly required to by law as a direct result of such proceedings as a court order or a legal process.

**Third party cookies**

This site use third-party advertising companies to serve ads whenever a visitor comes to this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Consent**

By using our site, you consent and are in agreeance with our privacy policy.

**Changes**

Should our privacy policy ever be changed, updated, or expanded, any revisions to will be posted on this page.

**Contacting Us**

To contact me, send me an email at _ **howtodoinjava@gmail.com**_  

The following two tabs change content below.

  * Bio
  * Latest Posts

I love to discuss things and that’s exactly why I am here. In java, I have around 7 Yrs of experience which has only increased my hunger for learn. In this blog, i will be writing on different topics occasionally, and would really love to engage in some meaningful serious discussions with you folks. I hope to hear from all your lovely people.

http://howtodoinjava.com/wp-content/uploads/Java_logo-75x100.png

**What information do we collect?**

In this website, you are required to :  
1) enter your email address to get latest updates from this blog directly into your email box for free  
2) enter your name, email and website you own, when you put a comment on any post

Apart from this, you are not expected to put any personal information anywhere in this blog, including comments, which you may not want to make public.

**How do we use your information?**

This website will use your email addresses to send you notifications about new posts when they are published. You may also get weekly updates which will include all happenings in last week in form of a guide.

When you leave a comment of this website, you may get a notification regarding your comment approval/denial.

**Disclose of information**

I do not sell, trade, release, or otherwise transfer information partially or in its entirety to any third party unless pursuant of an investigation of suspected unlawful, harmful, or otherwise illegal activity (including enforcement of our site’s policies, protection to our rights, property, and/or safety or the rights, property, and/or safety of others), or strictly required to by law as a direct result of such proceedings as a court order or a legal process.

**Third party cookies**

This site use third-party advertising companies to serve ads whenever a visitor comes to this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Consent**

By using our site, you consent and are in agreeance with our privacy policy.

**Changes**

Should our privacy policy ever be changed, updated, or expanded, any revisions to will be posted on this page.

**Contacting Us**

To contact me, send me an email at _ **howtodoinjava@gmail.com**_  

The following two tabs change content below.

  * Bio
  * Latest Posts

I love to discuss things and that’s exactly why I am here. In java, I have around 7 Yrs of experience which has only increased my hunger for learn. In this blog, i will be writing on different topics occasionally, and would really love to engage in some meaningful serious discussions with you folks. I hope to hear from all your lovely people.

 Lokesh Gupta Lokesh Gupta lokeshgupta1981@gmail.com Administrator I love to discuss things and that’s exactly why I am here. In java, I have around 7 Yrs of experience which has only increased my hunger for learn. In this blog, i will be writing on different topics occasionally, and would really love to engage in some meaningful serious discussions with you folks. I hope to hear from all your lovely people. How to do in JAVA
